("Come On Eileen" by
Dexys Midnight Runners)
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ Poor old Johnnie Ray ♪
♪ Sounded sad upon the radio ♪
♪ But he moved a million hearts in mono ♪
♪ Our mothers cried ♪
♪ Sang along ♪
♪ Who'd blame them ♪
♪ You've grown ♪
♪ So grown ♪
♪ Now I must say more than ever ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ Too-ra-loo-ra too-ra-loo-rye aye ♪
♪ And we can sing just like our fathers ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ Oh I swear ♪
♪ At this moment you mean everything ♪
♪ You in that dress ♪
♪ My thoughts I confess ♪
♪ Verge on dirty ♪
♪ Oh come on Eileen ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ These people 'round here ♪
♪ Wear beaten-down eyes
sunk in smoke-dried faces ♪
♪ They're so resigned
to what their fate is ♪
♪ But not us ♪
♪ No not us ♪
♪ We are far too young and clever ♪
♪ Remember ♪
♪ Too-ra-loo-ra too-ra-loo-rye aye ♪
♪ Eileen I'll hum this tune forever ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ Oh I swear what ♪
♪ At this moment you mean everything ♪
♪ You in that dress ♪
♪ My thoughts I confess ♪
♪ Yes they're dirty ♪
♪ Ah come on Eileen ♪
♪ You in that dress ♪
♪ Honey yes I confess ♪
♪ Ah come on Eileen ♪
♪ Please ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ta-loo-rye-aye ♪
♪ More than ever ♪
♪ Let's sing one another ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ I said come on Eileen ♪
♪ Well you know how I feel ♪
♪ You know I'm pleasured ♪
♪ I said I'm pleasured
pleasured pleasured ♪
♪ I must say ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Toora loora loora ♪
♪ Too-rye-aye ♪
♪ Mm-Mm-Mm ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ It's clear how I feel ♪
♪ Well yes yes yes ♪
♪ I suppose it must be ♪
♪ Must say more than ever ♪
♪ Round here we've changed ♪
♪ I say ♪
♪ Toora loora toora loo-rye-aye ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ Yes I swear what ♪
♪ At this moment you mean everything ♪
♪ You in that dress ♪
♪ My thoughts I confess ♪
♪ Everything ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Oh come on oh come on oh come on ♪
♪ You in that dress ♪
♪ My thoughts must confess ♪
♪ Oh come on Eileen ♪
♪ Come on Eileen ♪